ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Publications /4283/001 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Publications
1989-2009
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Fleron, Lou Jean
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/4283/001 PUBS
9.67 cubic feet
9.7 linear ft.
Publications (documents).
9250169
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 11, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 05, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4283: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files /4283 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Audio-Visual Materials /4283 MB: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Memorabilia /4283 P: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Photographs /4283/001: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Files /4283/001 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Audio-Visual Materials /4283/001 MB: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Memorabilia /4283/001 (d): ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Born Digital Material /4283/002: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Files /4283/002 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Audio-Visual Materials /4283/002 P: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Photographs
Fleron, Lou Jean; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Extension and Public Service Division; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
9250169
- A Strong Union in a Changing World, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- UAW- Ford Automotive Industries Studies Pilot Program Development Proposal, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  November 11, 1991
- UAW- Ford Automotive Industries Studies Pilot Program Development Proposal, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  November 11, 1991. Copy 2
- UAW- Ford Automotive Industries Studies Pilot Program Development Proposal, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  November 11, 1991. Copy 3
- UAW- Ford Automotive Industries Studies Pilot Program Development Proposal: Excerpts, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- UAW- Ford Automotive Industries Studies Pilot Program Development Proposal: Excerpts, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  November 11, 1991. Copy 2.
- UAW- Ford Automotive Industries Studies Program Instructors Guide, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Ford: A Decade of Growth, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- UAW-Ford Joint Program Key Documents, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Black Lake, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Diversity: UAW-Ford New Employee Orientations Program, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- UAW-Ford Joint Program Key Documents, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- UAW-Ford Report, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  September 1996
- UAW-Ford Automotive Industry Studies Geographic Programs Proposal, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  February 5, 1996
- UAW- Ford Automotive Industries Studies Geographic Pilot Program Evaluation Report, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  June 1996
- UAW- Ford Automotive Industries Studies Geographic Pilot Program Final Evaluation Report, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  July 1996
- UAW-Ford National Programs Center, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Focus on the People, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  June 1997
- University Programs, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- UAW- Ford Automotive Industries Studies Program, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Fueling the Future With Ford: The Electric Way, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- UAW-Ford National Education Development and Training Program Pocket Guide, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Making a Difference in Tomorrow's World, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Time of Our Life: Workbook, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Sharing Our Pride: EDTP 20th Anniversary, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- UAW-Ford Lifestyle Management: Planning Your Future Ready or Not, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- A Tribute to Auto Workers, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Take the AIS Tour, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- AIS Workbook Supplement, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- UAW-Ford Automotive Industry Studies Workbook, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- UAW-Ford Automotive Industry Studies Workbook, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  Copy 2
- UAW-Ford Automotive Industry Studies Workbook, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- UAW-Ford Automotive Industry Studies Workbook, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Cornell ILR Programs in Buffalo (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Cornell ILR Programs in Buffalo (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Copy 2.
- UAW-Ford Lifestyle Management: Planning Your Future (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Coordinator's Manual
- UAW-Ford Lifestyle Management: Planning Your Future (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Coordinator's Manual. Copy 2
- UAW-Ford Lifestyle Management: Planning Your Future (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Legal Services and Benefits Guide
- Power 2 Beat the Competition: UAW and Ford Fight Back (Box 2, Folder 6)
- UAW-Ford Successful Training Techniques for Joint Programs (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Saginaw Division, General Motors, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Training Post, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- The Voice of Labor, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Plant Five Newspaper, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Horizons, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- UAW-GM Local Paid Educational Leave: Sections 1-5, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- UAW-GM Local Paid Educational Leave: Sections 6-12, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Quality: Working in the Auto Industry, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Quality: Working in the Auto Industry, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Quality: Working in the Auto Industry, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Copy 3.
- Quality: Working in the Auto Industry, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Copy 4.
- Building Better Workplace Relationships by Valuing Diversity, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Phase II Employee Orientation Participant Manual, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- E2: Education for Empowerment (Box 2, Folder 21)
- American Axle and Manufacturing: Forging New World Driveline Standards (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Attitudes of Labor Leaders Toward Labor Cooperatives: A Survey of the United States, The United Kingdom, and Italy, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Niagara Mohawk-IBEW Agreement, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Industry Education Program, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Unions and International Competition: European Unions and EC92, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  Sections 1-3
- Unions and International Competition: European Unions and EC92, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  Section 4
- Unions and International Competition: European Unions and EC92, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  Sections 5-7
- The EFTA Countries and the European Single Market: A Labor Perspective, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- The New Generation, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Telecommunications Transformation: Implications for Work and Employment, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- What's Afta NAFTA?: Unions and the Response to Free Trade in the Western Hemisphere, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- It's Your Business: Advanced Industry Education Program, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Supervision in a Changing Work Environment, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Boston Edison, 1994-1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Electric Power Industry Deregulation: Understanding the Issues, Shaping Opinions, and Influencing Policy Makers, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Sections 1-19
- Electric Power Industry Deregulation: Understanding the Issues, Shaping Opinions, and Influencing Policy Makers, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Sections 20-28
- Profiles on Electricity Issues, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Renegotiating the Regulatory Contract: Opportunism, Municipalization, and Bypass in the US Electric Power Industry, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Are You Ready to Compete, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Electrical Utility Restructuring Activity, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- National Residential Consumer Monitor: Analytical Report, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Niagara Mohawk, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Profiles of Competition, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- The Restructuring of the Electric Power Industry: A Capsule of Issues and Events, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- The States: Leaders in Electric Power Industry Restructuring, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Status Report on Electric Industry Municipalization and Bypass Activities, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- The Truth About the HVACR Industry, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Taking Charge: Electric Industry Education Summit, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Cutting Taxes, Creating Jobs: The Decline and Revival of Upstate New York, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Industry Advertising: October 1998 - January 1999 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Looking Forward: The Next Ten Years in the Electric Industry, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Electric Industry Outlook, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Electric Shock: Labor-Management Relations in Deregulated Electric Utilities, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- National Energy Policy, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Co-Operation: An Editorial Without Words (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Taking Charge: Electric Industry Education (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Taking Charge: Electric Industry Education (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Communication (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Olin Corporation Annual Reports, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Bethlehem Steel Impact Study: Survey of Workers, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Outokumpu Annual Reports, 1989-1994 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- The Copper Courier, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Demographic Information for the Greater Cedar Rapids Area, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- INCRA Technology Program Progress Reports, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Index of the INCRA Technology Division Publications, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Inside Out, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Industry Education Program: Outokumpu American Brass and USWA Local 593 Progress Report, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Phelps Dodge Annual Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Outokumpu American Brass Industry Education Program, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Outokumpu American Brass Industry Education Program, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Outokumpu American Brass Industry Education Program, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Implementing Self-Directed Work Teams: Workbooks, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Outokumpu News, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Kumpu, 1994-1999 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- It's Your Business, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- The Communicator, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- 2001: A Vision in Progress, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Connections: Succeeding in an Interrelated World, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Connections: Succeeding in an Interrelated World, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Cooperation at Work (Box 4, Folder 17)
- We and Our Corporate Culture (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Telecommunications: A Vital Infrastructure for the New New York, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Analysis of the Economic Effect of the Network Modernization on New York State's Economy, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Information Networking for Global Competition: Creating Tomorrow in Telecommunications, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Measuring the Economic Effect of Modernizing New York State's Telecommunications Infrastructure, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Outline of the Position of New York Newspaper Publishers Association Regarding New York State's Future Telecommunications Policy, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- The Telephone Lifeline Act: The "Trigger Mechanism" in the Act, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Why Manage the Arts, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- New York's Big Picture: Executive Summary, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- New York's Big Picture: Assessing New York's Position in Film, Television, and Commercial Production, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Redefining Texts: Expanding Learning Through the Arts, 2003-2006 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Know When To Fold 'Em: Time to Walk Away From NYC's Corporate Retention Game, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- State Policies to Assist Working-Poor Families, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Technical Proposal: Buffalo Niagara Enterprise Labor Market Assessment, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Privatization Without Competition Equals Huge Losses, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- WIED Team Planning Meeting, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Buffalo Child Care Means Business, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Workforce, Industry, and Economic Development: New Focus on Innovative Economic Solutions, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  Environment Scan
- Bridging the Gap: Training Needs Assessment of the Immigrant Workforce in Onondaga County, NY, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Putting Local Democracy to Work, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Catch That Bus: Reverse-Commute Challenges Facing Low Income Inner-City Residents of Onondaga County, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Champions at Work: Executive Summary (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Cornell Economic Development Resource Guide (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Women First for 135 Years: 1858-1993 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Forward Thinking, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Blueprint, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Farms, Communities, and Collaboration: A Guide to Resolving Farm-Neighbor Conflict, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- The Clear Picture on Clear Channel Communications, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Consolidation and Labor in Arts and Entertainment: A Peek at Clear Channel, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- A Great Potential: The Great Lakes as a Regional Renewable Energy Source, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Owners at Work: Ohio Employee Ownership Center, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Perspectives on Work, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Surviving a Layoff, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Telecommunications 2004: Strategy, HR Practices, and Performance (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Champions Network Newsletter, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- 1199 SEIU Grievance Guide, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Basic Cable Television Industry Research and Corporate Profiles, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Comprehensive Three-Year Plan: Onondaga County, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Erie County Community Collation: A Commonsense Approach to the Erie County Budget Crisis, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- The Future For Union Sheet Metal Construction, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Renewables 2005: Global Status Report (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Socio-Economic Characteristics of the Construction Workforce in the New York City Area, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- ILR School Pamphlets, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Hottest Place to Be Cool: Business and Labor Energy at Work, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Brainpower to Hydropower: All the Energy You Need, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- The State of the Living Wage in Buffalo, New York, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- The Human Face of Economic Development, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Coming Together at Cornell: School of Industrial and Labor Relations Extension and Public Service (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Getting Out the Vote (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Getting Out the Vote: A Guide for Workplace Volunteers (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Mining Hidden Assets (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Champions at Work Case Studies (Box 5, Folder 34)
- The Workforce Practices and Labor-Management Relations in Western New York Survey: Employee and Union Surveys, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  August 8, 2000
- The Workforce Practices and Labor-Management Relations in Western New York Survey: Employee and Union Surveys, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  August 8, 2000. Copy 2.
- The Workforce Practices and Labor-Management Relations in Western New York Survey: Employee and Union Surveys, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  August 8, 2000. Copy 3.
- The Workforce Practices and Labor-Management Relations in Western New York Survey: Employee and Union Surveys, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  Champion Cases. September 5, 2000
- The Workforce Practices and Labor-Management Relations in Western New York Survey: Employee and Union Surveys, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  Champion Cases. September 5, 2000. Copy 2.
- Champions at Work (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Policy Brief: Upstate's Recent Arrivals, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  January 2008
- Getting Out the Vote: A Guide for Workplace Volunteers (Box 5, Folder 42)
- A progressive Economic Development Agenda for Shared Prosperity, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  June 2006
- American Energy: The Renewable Path to Energy Security, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  September 2006
- Time for a Global Welfare System?, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  May-June 2007
- Beyond Disasters: Creating Opportunities for Peace, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- The Economic Benefits of High-Quality Early Education Programs: What Makes the Difference?, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  February 2006
- A Guide to Calculating the Cost of Quality Early Care and Education, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  May 2006
- Collective Management of Early Childhood Programs (Box 5, Folder 49)
- A Proposal for Achieving High Returns on Early Childhood Development, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Downtown Buffalo Child Care Assessment, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  March 27, 2006
- Telecommunications 2004: Strategy, HR Practices, and Performance (Box 6, Folder 1)
- New York State Self-Sufficiency Standard: Erie County, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- A Lifetime of Assets: Building Families, Communities, and Economies, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Benefits and Low Wage Work, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Working Together for Public Service, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Strategies and Methods for Public Sector Labor-Management Committees, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Strategies and Methods for Public Sector Labor-Management Committees, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- The Ultimate Atlas, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Volume 2
- Governance in Erie County: A Foundation for Understanding and Action, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Where the Action Is: Preparation for a Running Start, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Fact Book, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Employee Involvement Committee: Results Book, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Austria Documentation, 1983-1989 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Euopaisches Gewerkschaftsinstitut, 1985-1991 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  German.
- Osterreich Und Der Binnenmarkt, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Toward a Model of Community Activity, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Metro Buffalo Facts, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Local Government Cooperative Service Provision (Box 6, Folder 18)
- H. Carl McCall, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- The Constitution, 1985-1988 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- A School Is A Workplace (Box 6, Folder 21)
- What Work Requires of School, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- A New Compact for Learning, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- The New American Worker, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Local Union History, 1974-1985 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- The First Sixty Years: The Story of The National Labor Relations Board, 1935-1995 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Plant Closings: Issues, Politics, and Legislation, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Plant Closings: Resources for Public Officials, Trade Unionists, and Community Leaders, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Rational Industrialization: An Economic Development Agenda for Detroit, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- UAW Educational Materials, 1974-1979 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- USWA, 1980-1988 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- 50 Years of Challenge, 1942-1992: USWA 26th Constitutional Convention (Box 6, Folder 32)
- USWA 25th Constitutional Convention, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- "The River Ran Red" Homestead, 1892, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Steelworkers Leaflets (Box 6, Folder 35)
- USWA Health Care, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- USWA Women (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Steelworkers in Transition: Adjusting to a Contracting Job Market, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- At the Centre, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- USWA Audit Report, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  January 1 to December 31, 1989
- The Employer and the Workplace Hazardous Materials Information System (WHMIS), 1987 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- People's Daily World, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  August 25, 1990
- Revolutions In Europe: Thoughts for the American Trade Union Movement, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- The World After 1989: Workers and Unions in the New Economic Order, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- USWA: My Union With Pride (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Steel Shots, 1982-1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- The Steelworkers Oldtimer, 1986-1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Steelabor, 1988-1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Steelabour, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- USWA Civil Rights (Box 7, Folder 6)
- USWA Child Care, 1982-1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Leadership in the Local Union (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Many Faces Looking Forward, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- UAW-Ford Automotive Industry Studies: Pilot Program Development, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Hamilton, Houston, Lownie Architects (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Quality: Communications Connections on the Practical Side, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- The EFTA Countries and the European Single Market: A Labor Perspective, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Disability Employment Policies and Practice in US Federal Government Agencies, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Partnership and Change, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Promoting Mutual Respect: Preventing Inappropriate Workplace Behavior, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Hiring the Best for ILR Extension: Bias Free Interviewing (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Discovery Workbook, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Building Your Steelworkers Local, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- United Steelworkers of America Pamphlets, 1972-1986 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- United Steelworkers of America Pamphlets (Box 7, Folder 21)
  Undated
- United Steelworkers of America Flyers and Broadsides (Box 7, Folder 22)
- The Equal Employment Opportunity Act of 1972 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Buffalo Labor Calendar, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Hazards Communication, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Ontario Federation of Labor (Box 7, Folder 26)
  English and French
- RAC Report, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- American Steel Jobs in South Africa, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Latin America (Box 7, Folder 29)
- This Union Is For You: The Grievance Committee Handbook (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Declining Job-Based Health Coverage in the United States and California: A Crisis for Working Families, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Perspectives on Work, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- An Interest Based Approach to Problem Solving, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- USWA Constitutions, 1986-1990 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Serving Steelworkers in Times of Change, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- USWA Ready Reference Guide for Local Union Leadership (Box 7, Folder 36)
- USWA Workers Compensation Committees for Local Unions (Box 7, Folder 37)
- USWA in Canada (Box 7, Folder 38)
- USWA Politics (Box 7, Folder 39)
- USWA Employee Ownership, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Joint Advisory Committee on Productivity, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- People in Steel, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Steelmaking and the Environment, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- An Evening Wit Mike Mazuca, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- America at Work, 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- "The Buzz" Branch 3 Newsletter, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- "The Buzz" Branch 3 Newsletter, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- "The Buzz" Branch 3 Newsletter, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- "The Buzz" Branch 3 Newsletter, 2004-2009 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Dispute Resolution Times, 2000-2003 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- ILR Alumni Bulletin, 2001-2004 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- ILR Connections (Box 8, Folder 8)
- IUE-CWA News, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- New York State AFL-CIO Unity, 1997-2003 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Reflections on Progress at Work, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Why Do We Spend So Much Money?, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Index to Occupational Safety an Health Publications and Audio-Visual Productions, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Local 1000 News, 1959-1981 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Our Union Speaks, 1945-1946 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Local 1000, 25 Years of Service, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- UE Labor News, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- More Than a Century of Dedication to Workers in the Glass Industry, 1878-1978 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- A Partnership in the Workplace, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- History of the American Flint Glass Workers' Union, 1978-1957 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- AFGWU Local no.570 Agreement, 1987-1990 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- AFGWU Local no.1000 Bylaws, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- AFGWU Local no.1000 Agreements, 1965-1969 (Box 8, Folder 23)